Mediasoittimesi ei tue jaksossa käytettyä tekstitysformaattia.
Ne tuskin tulevat toimimaan oikein.
Valitse jokin suositelluista mediasoittimista, mieluusti mpv:
https://mpv.io
Videoeditointi
Kanes31
Laadunvarmistus
fedew
Gab
Galaxy 9000
Gol D. Rocks
Pepperjack
fedew
Gab
Galaxy 9000
Gol D. Rocks
Pepperjack
fedew
Gab
Galaxy 9000
Gol D. Rocks
Pepperjack
Grafiikat
Datenshi
Äänieditointi
Halee
Karaoketekstitykset
Gab
KaitouYahiko
Tekstitysten Ajoitus
Gab
Tekstitysten Ladonta
Tekstitysten tarkistus
Gab
Zenef
Käännös
Sangatsu Manga
Kanes31
Mediasoittimesi ei tue jaksossa käytettyä tekstitysformaattia.
Ne tuskin tulevat toimimaan oikein.
Valitse jokin suositelluista mediasoittimista, mieluusti mpv:
https://mpv.io
Kohti Syvyyksiä
Sabaody-Saaret
Velitsu! Hankala kaivaa!
Niin, no...
Onhan saari paljolti puunjuurten päällä.
Armoa! Älkää haudatko meitä!
Me tehdään mitä vain,
kunhan säästätte henkemme!
Me vain toteltiin kapteenia!
Sitä Blackin kurjimusta...!
Mie kuulkaas ajattelin...
että Olkihatun toveriksi päästyämme...
voitaisiin sisältäpäin...
listiä koko sakki vapaasti.
Drip!
Hei, lopeta! Sehän kuolee!
Onko sullakin pirunmarjavoimat?!
K-Käskin lopettaa!
Jes! Osuipas...
Häh? Mitä hittoa... Logia-tyyppikö?!
Ja kuinkas sitten kävikään!
Kyllä kahdessa vuodessa
naama ja kroppa ehtii muuttua, ajattelin...
Olkihattu-piraatti...
Mutta eipä mitään!
Kyseessä oli vain puijari!
Salliiko Jumala tällaista, Coribou?
Kaivan, kaivan!
Jetsulleen.
Haudataan kaikki tyynni!
Voi jumalat!
Myö hautaamme joka iikan
näistä tyhmyreistä!
Lopettakaa! Älkää tappako meitä!
Mutta näin ikiomin silmin myös
aidon Olkihattu-Luffyn!
Valeolkihattujen Kokoontumispaikka
Kerroinhan jo. Ei siinä tilanteessa voinut muuta.
Eteen asettui "Haades" Rayleigh!
Mies pysäytti setä Kizarunkin!
Mitä meidän muka pitäisi tehdä?
Aukiolta pääsivät livahtamaan Caribou-veljekset
joukkoineen, ja osa valeolkihatuista.
Nappasimme kaikki muut, mutta aidot
Olkihatut vaurioittivat pahasti kahta pasifistaa.
Kyllä, prototyyppejä, jotka kaksi
vuotta sitten panivat heidät ahtaalle.
Pasifistojen voimat ei ole muuttuneet...
vaan sen porukan!
Piileskelyaikanaan he ovat
kehittyneet rajusti!
Varmistakaa, että päämaja
Uudessa Maailmassa tajuaa!
Olkihatun sakki on taas iskukykyinen!
Lähtö kävi äkkiä.
Pikku Monkey ja muut olivat varttuneet...
Katselit siis.
Toki, olenhan fani.
Ray... Muistelitko kenties jotain?
No...
Itse asiassa...
Hoi! Komea pursi!
Kunhan pöllin.
Asun tällä, kun taloni paloi poroksi.
Ahaa. Mikä on nimi?
Rayleigh.
Mä olen Roger!
Kohtalo toi meidät yhteen, Rayleigh!
Kohtalo?
Keikautetaanko yhdessä
maailma ylösalaisin?
Häh?
Maailma?
Mikä luulet olevasi?
Ala kalppia!
Ehkä tässä maailmassa
ei olekaan sattumia.
Tapahtumat ja siteet muodostavat kuvioita,
kuin kaikki olisi jo ennalta saneltua.
Oli miten oli, Luffysta on tullut mies,
jolle tuo hattu sopii aina vain paremmin!
Elämällä saattaa olla vielä jotain
hauskaa tarjottavaa...
Sabaodyn Lähistöllä, Meren Alla
Pinta on jo noin kaukana.
Mitkä näkymät!
Sukellusveneeseen ei saisi
näin leveää ikkunaa!
Vajoamme aina vian syvemmälle!
Onko ihan varma, että vesi ei tule sisälle?!
Ihmismaailma tuntuu jotenkin
kaukaiselta... Jännittää!
P-Päästäänkö vielä takaisin maan päälle?
E-Ei sillä että pelkäisin...
Meri on tosi kaunis...!
Vilkaiskaapa vierellemme!
Puita... Ei kun juuria!
Tosiaan.
Kun asiaa ajattelee, koko Sabaodyhan
on iso mangrovemetsä...
Luonto näyttää mahtinsa!
Melkein poksahtavat silmät ulos kallosta!
Ah, mutta eihän minulla niitä ole.
Mä näin jo.
Väärällä laivalla!
Pää kii ja anna toisten vaikuttua!
Juuret ulottuvat pohjaan saakka...
Tämä valtavuus vetää sanattomaksi.
Jo riitti minulle!
Hei, Chopper...
Puun takana on jotain!
Täh?
Vau, se on iso!
Tosi jänskää!
Seikkailu meren alla!
Kuin näkisi unta!
Oho! Kaloja!
Melkein saan kiinni..!
Toikin näyttää makoisalta.
Nyt loppuu tuollainen!
Entä jos kupla puhkeaa?!
Saatte köniin jos teette noin vielä!
Nami-neiti, kertokaa, miten pitää toimia,
ennen kuin nuo hölmöävät jotain.
Olet oikeassa, Sanji!
Herra Rayleigh kirjoitti ohjeet.
No niin, kaikki! Selitän...
Liikkui!
Livekaunotar!
– Sanji!
Hajoaa! Hajoaa! Hajoaa!
Miten purskauksesta noin voi lentää?
– Täh?!
– Sanji putkahti mereen!
Kiehtovaa.
Kupla ei hajoa huolimatta näin syvällä
veden alla vallitsevasta valtavasta paineesta,
mutta asiat voivat kulkea
sen läpi tuosta noin vain.
Sanji!
Tule takaisin!
Meri vie voimat...
– Tsemppiä!
Mikä sinua vaivaa, Sanji?!
Kuin et enää kestäisi naisia!
Ei se ole sinunlaistasi!
Surullista...
Mitä Sanji, naisrakas ystävämme,
on näiden vuosien aikana kokenut...?
Ja jos tällä menolla kohtaamme
merenneitoja, hän vielä vuotaa kuiviin.
En voi olla kuin huolissani.
Täytyy saada lisää verta Nereidisaarella...
Onkohan nereidien ja merenmiesten
veri kuin ihmisillä?
Sunnyn päällyste toimii samalla tavalla
kuten Sabaodyn kuplat,
kuten juuri näimme. Niinkö?
Älä sä vain viileänä analysoi kuplia!
Yes, Robin's right.
Basically, they're the same.
It stretches to a certain point and beyond that, it allows things to get through.
Which means if we fire a gun or a cannon
at a creature that attacks us,
the bubble won't break.
Huh?
Then on what occasion would it break?
As you can imagine, when there are
too many holes at once, it'll break.
For example, if we are bitten
by a sea king's fangs, it'll be trouble.
– It's coming from behind!
They're fighting... We're safe!
Or if the ship itself breaks up
by crashing into a rock or a trench,
the broken mast or planking will break
the bubble, and that also spells danger.
So we have to be careful
with creatures and obstacles in the sea.
As long as we don't do anything
foolish from inside, it'll be fine.
I see! It's tougher than I thought!
But...
of the ships that head
for Fishman Island, 70% of them...
end up sinking. So be cautious.
– What's gonna happen?!
With my Gatling, I can catch
a whole school of fish!
Then let's see which of us can catch more fish!
Weren't you guys listening
to what Nami said?!
"Too many holes" is no good!
Don't ever try it again or I'll kill you!
Damn!
Hachi said he'd show us the way to Fishman Island,
so I thought it was gonna be a safe trip!
Oh, yeah!
They gave me a lot of lunches!
Since Sanji is sick, let's eat these, everybody!
I'm so starved!
My bones are starved!
Nami, the ship is gonna be stable for a while?
Don't we have to do anything?
Nope.
We just have to ride
this big sea current for now.
So, yeah, we can continue on
like this for a while.
We don't have much to do until later.
Then we have a little time, huh?
There's something that
I have to tell you all about.
– The robot's secrets?!
You have more secrets?!
What can you transform into?!
Or you have a secret weapon?!
Tell us, robot brother!
Super Armored Me!
No, I'm afraid...
I'm afraid it's not about that-robo.
– Wow, cool! He speaks Robotese!
This is what I wanna tell you about.
Go ahead and eat while you're listening.
Hachi told us that he would show us
the way to Fishman Island,
but he was severely injured at Sabaody
and placed under medical care at Fishman Island.
He got injured for the same reason as Duval.
He had been protecting the Thousand Sunny.
When the Marines found out
about the Sunny two years ago,
those two faced fierce battles
but were taken out of commission.
Huh?
Then how did the ship
remain undamaged after that?
There was someone else who fought for it.
There was someone else?
He's the one who separated us two years ago.
The big Warlord: Bartholomew Kuma!
I couldn't believe my eyes
when I got to the Sunny a few days ago...
I've been expecting you.
What are you doing here?!
Mission accomplished.
There isn't even a scratch on the Sunny.
And Rayleigh told me later...
I work for the Revolutionary Army.
Since I have a connection with them,
I wanna let them get away from here.
I think you guys half expected that.
He saved our lives!
And after we vanished from the island,
Kuma visited Rayleigh and told him...
I...
don't have much time left.
I don't know what made him obey the Marines,
but he agreed to be a guinea pig and let his body
be modified into a cyborg piece by piece.
He somehow lost his personality
before the Summit War.
But I don't think he could guess what
each of us would do after we get separated!
Even so, he waited for us
at the ship without his personality?
He made Dr. Vegapunk, who modified him,
agree to program a mission into his mind.
"Defend the pirate ship until the day that
one of the Straw Hats comes back to the ship."
That's why, for the past two years,
without his own memory,
he had been carrying out his own orders,
as a human weapon, waiting for us.
That's insane.
Why did he do such a thing for us?
Terms like "connection," "Revolutionary Army,"
remind me about Luffy's father,
the leader of the Revolutionary Army.
I don't know my father that well,
but that bear-like guy was a good guy, huh?
Kuma...
There is no mistake that he's the one
who gave us the past two worthwhile years.
We can't even ask him why he did it,
but just remember that.
Bartholomew Kuma turned out
to be one of our greatest allies.
But even if we meet him again,
Kuma is now a heartless human weapon.
That's all I have to say.
I'm grateful, but there are still some mysteries.
I hope we can find out his motive one day.
"Ally"?
Oh, you woke up, Sanji.
Eat lunch! It's from the Isle of Women!
Isle of Women?
Is that Kuma guy really an ally?
Don't you realize where I was
for the past two years?
What kind of training were you doing
at a dream island full of women, Luffy?
Now, now, Sanji.
I don't know what you've been through, but let's enjoy the voyage now!
Do you wanna sing with me?
Stop trying to cheer me up! I feel pathetic!
Brother, there he is. Straw Hat.
I can see that, you fool!
I'm gonna join them this time for sure!
How deeply are we submerged now?
It's getting darker and darker.
We went through the euphotic zone,
and we're at the bottom of the twilight zone.
It must be more than
a thousand meters below.
It's really quiet.
It feels different from submersibles.
It feels like flying in the sky.
Whale! There is a whale!
Laboon! Laboon!
No, that's old man Whitebeard!
There's something
at six o'clock! Is it a creature?
No...
Are you guys all ready?!
Yes, brother!
– Yes, yes!
The target is right there!
It's easier to just destroy their ship
and let it be swallowed by the sea,
but that's no good because
they won't know who did it to them.
We gotta cut their heads off and bring them back
to show the world what Caribou is capable of!
– Yes!
They're not ready to fight!
It's a complete surprise attack!
Don't make a mistake, guys!
– Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Hey, guys! There is a ship
kind of thing coming from behind!
What?
A ship?
It's coming toward us!
Charge!
It's a pirate ship!
They're pushing against us!
Go away! The bubble is gonna pop!
No! They're gonna come through the bubble!
Who are they?
Run!
Hard to port!
Go, sea cow!
They're coming after us!
That sound...
They're so persistent!
What do they want from us?
Stop!
The bubble is gonna pop!
You're doing great, sea cow!
– Yes!
Are they gonna come aboard?
Sea cow?
Wait a minute! That's...
The bubbles are joined!
Brother, now is the chance!
Alright!
Should we do it?!
– Yes!
Hey, Momoo!
Aren't you Momoo of the Arlong Pirates?
Do you remember me?
I'm Nami!
I was there at the Arlong Park!
Hey, Luffy...
Doesn't he look familiar?
Yeah?
Die, damn you!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Let's board their ship!
– Yes!
Whoa! He's coming through the bubble!
No, somebody's coming!
We gotta fight!
Guys!
Are you ready?!
– Yes!
While they're dumbfounded,
kill them all!
Let's go!
Yes!
Guys, follow my lead!
– What?!
What's the matter, sea cow?
Why, sea cow?
Oh no, we left Captain Caribou on that ship!
Brother!
Alright, by way of greeting,
fire the gatling gun!
Kill all the Straw Hats and...
Huh?
No! Don't throw me out into the water!
That's something you shouldn't do!
You have to value people's life!
The gods... The gods are watching
over you! Don't you think so?!
You're being inconsistent!
Weren't you gonna fire
a gatling gun and kill us all?!
No, that was just...
That was just a play on words.
That wasn't playing.
Who are you?
You must be the captain of the ship.
Oh, Roronoa Zoro!
No way! I'm not a captain!
I'm just...
I was forced to be a slave for them!
Oh, I'm sick of being on that ship!
Oh, yeah! This is great!
Can I stay on this ship for a little while?
Please?
Well, he is kind of pathetic...
No way! He just made it up!
What?! He just made it up?!
Hey, where did you find the sea cow
who was drawing your ship?
Oh...
Here is...
one fine cutie!
You're the Cat Burglar.
Stop looking at our navigator like that!
Nami!
You're safe... now!
That's getting to be a pain!
I just caught that sea monster somewhere...
Experienced people
have those animals pull their ship.
What?!
Is that so?
Stop! Stop, sea cow!
What happened?
Brother! I'll save you!
I wanna find a sea monster.
Hey, Luffy!
What are you up to?
Let's start his rehabilitation
with some less stimulating pics.
Hey, Nami.
We're not exactly heading
where the log pose is pointing.
Yeah, that's fine.
The right course should be
southwest of where it's pointing.
It's faster to go straight.
Why should we do that?
If you go straight, you'd be
taken away by the sea current
and get stuck by a volcano
or an undersea mountain.
What?! Volcano!
It's scary to be in the water!
But I thought the sea currents
in the Grand Line were volatile.
Is there any stable current?
Yes, just one.
This is good.
Stay calm.
Everyone! It's gonna get colder from
here on out, so wear a coat or something.
Yes, it's getting chilly. I can feel it on my skin.
Oh, but I don't...
You're a skeleton, so you don't have skin.
Chopper...
You can't do that...
You can't steal my line...
Are we going somewhere cold?
Not the deep sea?
Don't you know that the water
in the deep sea is cold?
Like in a bathtub, hot water goes up
and cold water goes down.
Oh yeah? I'm not a big fan
of baths so I wouldn't know.
I see.
If the sea is the same as a bathtub,
it's gonna get colder as you go deeper.
The temperature isn't the only difference.
You're still depressed?!
In the deep layer of the sea...
Nyky-
sijainti
Pinta-
virtaus
Syvänmeren
Virtaus
Nyky-
sijainti
Pinta-
virtaus
Syvänmeren
Virtaus
Nyky-
sijainti
Pinta-
virtaus
Syvänmeren
Virtaus
Nyky-
sijainti
Pinta-
virtaus
Syvänmeren
Virtaus
Nyky-
sijainti
Pinta-
virtaus
Syvänmeren
Virtaus
Nyky-
sijainti
Pinta-
virtaus
Syvänmeren
Virtaus
there are giant currents called deep currents
that you don't get to see very often.
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Syvänmeren Virtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Those currents flow totally
independently from surface currents.
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
Nyky-
Sijainti
Pintavirtaus
There are currents under currents?!
You know a lot!
Because I'm really old!
All currents are connected.
One current flows eastward,
and the other one flows westward.
They could also flow upward or downward.
It's like a giant dragon.
Deep currents flow really slowly.
Once they flow to the deep sea,
it takes 2,000 years...
until they flow upward to the surface.
– Two thousand years?!
Yes...
That's why there are a number of myths
about the dark and undiscovered deep currents.
Monsters!
Curses!
Spirits of the dead!
What?!
There are ghosts in the deep sea?!
Huh? Really? I'm scared!
It's exciting!
Ghosts...
I don't know about that.
But we're gonna get on a downward flow.
That's how we get to the deep sea.
– So there's mystery currents...
You guys didn't understand a bit, did you?!
You wanna sing, Nami?
Shut up!
This is it!
Nami, I see it!
Yeah?
The mystery current?!
Where is it? Where is it?!
That's cool!
What is that?
So that's the downward current!
The Downwelling Current Plume!
How... cool!
It's like a massive...
waterfall in the sea!
The sea is "falling" far below!
At an extraordinary speed!
Interesting!
Nature is awesome!
What a spectacular stream!
I wonder how deep it is.
It's far greater than I had heard.
I can't see the bottom!
It's completely dark!
We're dead!
At that speed, we'd slam
into the bottom and die!
Is it really okay to go with the flow?
Don't worry about the ship.
Sunny is the strongest ship
built from Adam, the Jewel Tree.
No way!
I didn't know that it lives here...!
It's a demon that rules the realm of water!
And the enemy of the human race!
Straw Hats!
You should turn back now!
It's dangerous!
I had forgotten about you.
There is a monster!
It's...
It's right there...
Cut it out, guys!
B-Behind you...
What are you saying...
Is it...
behind me?
It's the kraken!
How huge! The monster octopus!
Looks like he broke a lot of ships!
Ships that had left for
the New World have been attacked!
Please! I don't wanna die!
Go back!
If you just wait for a few days, it would–
Shut up!
I have a good idea!
Let's tame him!
– Huh?